<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zug Property Development GmbH</title>
    <link>https://borecxx.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zug Property Development GmbH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 19:05:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://borecxx.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://borecxx.github.io/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borecxx.github.io/en/about/</guid>
      <description>The smart way of living Zug Property Development gmbh was founded in 2017 as a reaction to the market demand for affordable quality housing in Switzerland. We have a network of expert Architects and Builders who have many years of experience and have worked on numerous projects with many happy owners.
Company Concept Too often developers are attempting to maximize their profits by building large apartment complexes. Houses are considered luxury objects and are typically price restrictive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://borecxx.github.io/en/contact/contactdetails/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 19:05:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borecxx.github.io/en/contact/contactdetails/</guid>
      <description>Contact Form Name First Name Email Address Message    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luxurios Lifestyle-Houses - Bergdietikon</title>
      <link>https://borecxx.github.io/en/projects/bergdietikon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borecxx.github.io/en/projects/bergdietikon/</guid>
      <description>Überbauung Raistrasse, 8962 Bergdietikon Luxuriöse Lifestyle-Häuser im ruhigen Quartier, unweit von Zürich
An ruhiger Lage mit unverbaubarer Sicht, idyllische im Grünen eingebettet, entstehen per Ende 2019 vier luxuriöse Lifestyle Häuser mit exklusiver Ausstattung.
Jedes Haus verfügt über ein Untergeschoss mit und Keller und Wohn- und Küchenbereich, zwei Terrassen, nach Wahl mit Schwimmbad oder Whirlpool. Im Erdgeschoss befindet sich die Garage, der Eingangsbereich und 2 Schlafzimmer mit Badzimmer. Die Attika mit großer Terrasse kann zu einem großzügigen Masterschlafzimmer mit Wellnessbereich ausgebaut werden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Property</title>
      <link>https://borecxx.github.io/en/service/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borecxx.github.io/en/service/service1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Interested in purchasing property abroad for your holiday home or as an investment?
Zug Property Development International GmbH currently offers services in Greece.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Property Development</title>
      <link>https://borecxx.github.io/en/service/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borecxx.github.io/en/service/service3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a real shortage of houses in Switzerland. The market is overflowing with apartments and this doesn&amp;rsquo;t meet the demands of many families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>